https://www.tools-rvsupplies.com/privacy-statement.html

Screw Machine Bits Fraction, Number and Metric
HSS Fractions 1/16"-1/2"
HSS Wire Sizes 1 to 60
Cobalt Fractions 1/16"-1/2"
Bolts , Screws & Fastners
S-hooks, Cup Hooks etc.
0 items in cart
Subtotal:
Categories
Cutting Tools (77)
Drill Bits (5)
STEP DRILL (0)
DRILL BITS (43)
Screw Machine Bits Fraction, Number and Metric (1)
HSS Fractions 1/16"-1/2" (5)
HSS Wire Sizes 1 to 60 (10)
Cobalt Fractions 1/16"-1/2" (2)
Cobalt Wire Sizes 1 to 60 (7)
Metric (5)
ENDMILLS (2)
BURRS (15)
Automotive (47)
Filters (2)
Cable Ties (2)
Light Bulbs (10)
Battery & Electrial (23)
Trailer Wire And Conectors (4)
Fuses (1)
Alligator Clips & Cable Clamps (4)
Cleaners & Hydrometers (2)
Test Leads (3)
Testers (3)
RV Lights, Trailer Lights (22)
Exterior RV Lights (9)
Marker Lights (3)
Lenses for Lights (4)
Interior Lights (6)
Tools (142)
Air Tools & Accessories (13)
Saw & Grinding (1)
Buffing & Polishing (4)
Air Fittings and Accessories (4)
Scrapers & Knives (15)
Flash Lights (1)
Screw Dirvers (2)
Screw Tips (16)
Phillips Screw Tips (7)
Hand Tools (82)
Fastners (2)
Cutoff Wheels, Grinding, Sanding and Accessories (8)
Saw Blades (7)
Riveter and Accesories (1)
Punches and Prybars (5)
Pliers (12)
Brushes (31)
Electrical Testers (5)
Hex Keys (2)
Gas Prop (48)
Brackets (14)
Hareware (57)
Bolts , Screws & Fastners (0)
S-hooks, Cup Hooks etc. (5)
Snaps and Clips (9)
Grommets, Fasteners & Accessories (8)
Snap Pin (5)
LYNCH PIN (1)
Hitch Pine R-Pins trailer Balls (11)
Bungees (10)
Shackles (0)
Hobby Tools (40)
Files (2)
Tools (8)
Rotory Tools Accessories (6)
Scissors (4)
Dental Picks (1)
Arbors (1)
Hemostats (4)
Tweezers (13)
Lawn & Garden (18)
Garden Tools (2)
Hose Accessories (11)
Household (53)
Electronic & Electrical (4)
Rollers & Brushes (10)
Sewing (4)
Knives and Accessories (7)
Tweezers (13)
Scissors (0)
eBay Items (20)
Outdoor (31)
Bicycle Accessories (7)
Fishing (2)
Clips (2)
Bungee (13)
Tent Stakes (2)
Electrical (33)
Plugs and Extensions (9)
SOLDER ACCESSORIES (2)
Light Bulbs (10)
Crimping Tools & Wire Stripers (2)
BATTERY ACCESSORIES (5)
Alligator Clips & Cable Clamps (4)
Cable Ties (1)
RV Parts And Accessories (47)
Sanitation (8)
Hardware (20)
Latches (11)
Electrial (2)
Accessories (1)
Outdoor Gear (1)
RV Hardware (13)
Vents (3)
Door Holders (6)
Latches (0)
miscellaneous (1)
Other (4)
Top News
Nov 21, 2019
Flea Market
Big Pine Key flea market has reopened.
All news
Privacy Statement
Privacy at tools-rvsupplies.com
In general, when you visit our web site and access information you remain anonymous. Before we ask you for information, we will explain how this information will be used. We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. There are occasions where we will ask for additional information. Reason that we do this is to be able to better understand your needs, and provide you with services that we believe may be valuable to you.
Some areas of our site require registration to access, although typically all that’s requested is an e-mail address and some basic information about you, such as job function, how to contact you, use of computers and needs for solutions. However, whenever you give us information, you can elect not to receive any materials from us.
We only ask for specific types of personal information
In a few areas on our web site, we will ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit. However, it is completely optional for you to participate or not.
For example, we will request information from you when you:
Register into membership programs, contest programs or special promotion offer on tools-rvsupplies.com
Participate in an online survey or subscribe to a mailing list
Use the Store online ordering system.
In each of the instances above, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information, customer number and service tag number, basic information regarding your use of computer, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers.
We only use your personal information for specific purposes
The information you provided will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Novel. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on our web site and alert you to product changes, special offer, special campaign and event, updated information, other new products and services from Novel and even who won the contest program.
You can "unsubscribe" from our mailing list at any time
We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only Novel will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us at the time you give us your personal information.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is useful information, such as an e-mail address or user name, which is stored on your hard drive that enables your PC to "remember" some useful items when you return to a web site. At Novel, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your visit experience. Our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.pcclub.com. Some features may even require the presence of cookies to function properly. Novel has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using our web site.
Security Policy
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.
Links to Other Sites
Third party Internet sites and services accessible through pcclub.com have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Novel bears no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, Novel cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to Novel Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of Novel Online site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
If you have questions
Novel welcomes comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information, and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure. Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally update this policy and will not send out notice. All revisions will be posted to this site. All comments and questions should be sent to webmaster@tools-rvsuppies.com.
Return and Refund Policy
Privacy Statement
Terms & Conditions
Shipping
Sitemap
© 1985 - 2020 Novel Distributors. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
